Student Association of the State University of New York (SASU); Records apap046
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Student Assembly Meetings, 1973-1979; 2
  - Rules Committee, 1980 (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 48)
  - Rules of Order, Undated (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 49)
  - Staff, 1973 (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 50)
  - Structure, 1974 (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 51)
  - Structure, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 52)
  - Structure, 1978 (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 53)
  - Structure, 1980 (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 54)
  - Structure, Undated (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 55)
  - Third World Caucus, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 56)
  - Third World Caucus (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 57)
  - Third World Caucus (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 58)
  - Third World Caucus, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 59)
  - Third World Caucus, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 60)
  - Third World Caucus, Undated (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 61)
  - Women's Caucus, By-Laws, Undated (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 62)
  - Women's Caucus, Conference, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (2-Student Assembly Meetings), Folder 63)
- Membership Meetings, 1970-1980; 3
  This series contains minutes, memo's, and notices relating to the Membership Meetings, and provides information about the work of the committees, and changes in the organization's articles. The resolutions passed at these meetings illustrate the interests of the organization.
  - Minutes, 1970 (Box 1 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1971 (Box 1 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1972 (Box 1 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 3)
  - Memos, 1973 (Box 1 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1973 (Box 1 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 5)
  - Resolutions, 1973 (Box 1 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1974 (Box 1 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 7)
  - Membership List, 1974 (Box 1 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1975 (Box 1 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 9)
  - Memos, 1976 (Box 2 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1976 (Box 2 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 2)
  - Dues, 1976 (Box 2 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 3)
  - Memos, 1977 (Box 2 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 4)
  - Memos, 1978 (Box 2 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1979 (Box 2 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1980 (Box 2 (3-Membership Meetings), Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1970-1980; 4
  This series contains the correspondence of the SASU officers with SUNY administrators, state legislators, member schools, state and national student organizations, and student services providers. The correspondence with both state legislators and the SUNY administrators illustrates the growing respect given to SASU, as this student organization increased not only its size, but also, perhaps more important, its political sophistication. The correspondence with schools in the SUNY system documents SASU's struggle to gain the support of campuses throughout the state, the strategies used by SASU to publicize both its mission and its activities, and the continual budgetary constraints of both SASU and the member schools' student governments.
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1971 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1971 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1971 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1971 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1972 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1972 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1972 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1972 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1972 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Chairperson, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Board of Trustees, 1972-1976 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (1 of 13), 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (2 of 13), 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (3 of 13), 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (4 of 13), 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (5 of 13), 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (6 of 13), 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence (7 of 13), 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (8 of 13), 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (9 of 13), 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence (10 of 13), 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence (11 of 13), 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence (12 of 13), 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence (13 of 13), 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence Staff, 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Correspondence Chairperson, 1973 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Correspondence (1 of 6), 1974 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Correspondence (2 of 6), 1974 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Correspondence (3 of 6), 1974 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Correspondence (4 of 6), 1974 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Correspondence (5 of 6), 1974 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Correspondence (6 of 6), 1974 (Box 1 (4-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Correspondence (1 of 8), 1974 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (2 of 8), 1974 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (3 of 8), 1974 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (4 of 8), 1974 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (5 of 8), 1974 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (6 of 8), 1974 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (7 of 8), 1974 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (8 of 8), 1974 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Staff, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (1 of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (2 of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (3 of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (4 of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (5 of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (6 of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (7 of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (8 of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (9 of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence (1 0of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (11 of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (12 of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence (13 of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence (14 of 14), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence President, 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence Legislative Director (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence Legislative Director (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 2 (4-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Correspondence (1 of 12), 1976 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (2 of 12), 1976 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (3 of 12), 1976 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (4 of 12), 1976 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (5 of 12), 1976 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (6 of 12), 1976 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (7 of 12), 1976 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (8 of 12), 1976 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (9 of 12), 1976 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (10 of 12), 1976 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (11 of 12), 1976 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (12 of 12), 1976 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence President, 1976 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence Executive Vice-President, 1976-1977 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (1 of 7), 1977 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (2 of 7), 1977 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (3 of 7), 1977 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (4 of 7), 1977 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence (5 of 7), 1977 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (6 of 7), 1977 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (7 of 7), 1977 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence President, 1977 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence Vice President for Campus Affairs, 1977 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence Communications Director, 1977 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence Staff, 1977 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence President, 1977-1978 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Correspondence (1 of 5), 1978 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Correspondence (2 of 5), 1978 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Correspondence (3 of 5), 1978 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Correspondence (4 of 5), 1978 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Correspondence (5 of 5), 1978 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Correspondence Executive Vice President, 1978 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Correspondence Communications Director, 1978 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Correspondence Executive Vice President, 1979 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Correspondence Vice President for Campus Affairs, 1979 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Correspondence President, 1979-1980 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Correspondence Organizing Director, 1979-1980 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Correspondence (1 of 6), 1980 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Correspondence (2 of 6), 1980 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Correspondence (3 of 6), 1980 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Correspondence (4 of 6), 1980 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Correspondence (5 of 6), 1980 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Correspondence (6 of 6), 1980 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Correspondence Communications Director, 1980 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Correspondence Vice President for Campus Affairs, 1981 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 3 (4-Correspondence), Folder 49)
- Legislative Program, 1972-1980; 5
  This series documents the legislative concerns of the organization during the 1970s. The series contains SASU's annual legislative agenda, memos to State legislators and SASU officers at member schools, information packets distributed at the annual legislative conference, and periodic legislative reports compiled by SASU's legislative director. Since SASU did not start lobbying until December/January 1973-74, at which time it registered its legislative director with the New York State Secretary of State, most of the material covers the period 1974-80. SASU was especially involved in lobbying for the passage of the following legislation: mandatory provisions of absentee ballots, upon request, to eligible, unavoidably detained voters in primary elections (1974); the age of majority bill, lowering the age of majority from 21 to 18 (1974); the creation of the Tuition Assistance Program, (TAP), the nation's largest and most comprehensive student aid program (1974); mail voter registration (1975); a student trustee bill, drafted and initiated by SASU, which resulted in students becoming non-voting members on the SUNY Board of Trustees, the City University of New York Board of Higher Education, and on college and university councils and boards of trustees for all New York State's public colleges (this legislation was enacted despite strong opposition by many trustees and SUNY Central's legislative effort), (1975); the establishment of four students as voting members on the Higher Education Services Corporation's Board of Trustees, and four students on the HESC's Advisory Council, (the Board and the Advisory Council are responsible for determining administrative policies for HESC, which controls student financial aid), (1976); restoration of four of the five TAP programs cut in proposals by Governor Carey, (1976); the guarantee of all parliamentary rights, excluding the right to vote, for student members of the SUNY Board of Trustees, CUNY Board of Higher Education, and university and college councils for all public colleges, (these rights include, for example, the privileges of making and seconding motions, and attendance at executive sessions) (1977); marijuana decriminalization, preventing criminal penalties for the possession of small amounts of marijuana, (1977); an increase in the maximum allowable TAP eligible income, from $2,000 to $2,750 to allow for inflation, (1978); defeat of an attempt to cut off Medicaid funding for abortions, (1978); the repeal of the student health fee, (1979); and finally, after intensive lobbying by SASU, Student Trustees and student College Council members were granted the right to vote
  - Agenda, 1972 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 1)
  - Conference, 1972 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 3)
  - Legislative Reports, 1972 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 4)
  - Agenda, 1973 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 5)
  - Conference, 1973 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 6)
  - Evaluations, 1973 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 7)
  - Legislative Reports, 1973 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 8)
  - Memos, 1973 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 9)
  - Staff, 1973 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 10)
  - Agenda, 1974 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 11)
  - Conference, 1974 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 12)
  - Legislative Reports, 1974 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 13)
  - Memos to Legislature, 1974 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 14)
  - Memos to Staff, 1974 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 15)
  - Staff, 1974 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 16)
  - Agenda, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 17)
  - Conference, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 19)
  - Glass, Ray, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 20)
  - Legislative Reports, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 21)
  - Memos to Legislature, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 22)
  - Memos to Staff, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 23)
  - Agenda, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 24)
  - Conference, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 26)
  - Legislative Reports, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 27)
  - Memos to Legislature, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 28)
  - Memos to Staff, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 29)
  - Agenda, 1977 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 30)
  - Bill Sheets, 1977 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 31)
  - Conference, 1977 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 32)
  - Legislative Reports, 1977 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 33)
  - Memos to Legislature, 1977 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 34)
  - Memos to Staff, 1977 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 35)
  - General, 1978 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 36)
  - Memos to Legislature, 1978 (Box 1 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 37)
  - Agenda, 1979 (Box 2 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 1)
  - Conference, 1979 (Box 2 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 2 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 3)
  - Legislative Reports, 1979 (Box 2 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 4)
  - Memos, 1979 (Box 2 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 5)
  - Agenda, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 6)
  - Conference, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 7)
  - General, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 8)
  - Memos, 1980 (Box 2 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 9)
  - Agenda, 1981 (Box 2 (5-Legislative Program), Folder 10)
- Subject Files, 1970-1981; 6
  This series contains correspondence, internal and external SASU memos, information packets, press releases (1970-1980), reports relating to SASU's interests in student financial aid, in particular the Tuition Assistance Program, (1973-78), voter registration drives (1974-80), the SASU budget (1971-80), inter-collegiate athletics (1975-79), student services (1971-78), the Women's Caucus (1975-82), the Third World Caucus (1975-80), the organization of the SASU office in Albany (1973-81), student health services (1974-78), the State budget (1973-81), and the SUNY budget (1975-81).
  - Absentee Ballots, 1977 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Academic Grievance, 1972 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Accounts, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Accounts, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Accounts, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Accounts, 1980 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Activities Fee, 1971-1980 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action, 1974 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action, 1975 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action, 1977 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1975-1980 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 1977 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Apartheid, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Application for Authority, 1973 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Athletics Conference, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Bakke Case, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Basic Educational Opportunity Grants, 1976 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Bill of Rights, 1972 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Bill of Rights, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Boyer Case, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Boyer Interview, 1974 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Brodsky, Howard, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1970-1981 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - By-Laws, 1970; 1973-1975; 1977 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Campus Affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Campus Affairs, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Campus Coordinators, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Campus Justice, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Campus Security, 1974 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Campus Unrest, 1969 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Cards, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Carey/Samuels, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Carey, Hugh L., 1974 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Community College Student Association, 1976-1978 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Censorship, 1974 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1971-1973 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1974-1977 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Committees, 1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Committee on Organization, 1976-1978 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Committee Structure, 1973-1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Communications, 1972-1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Communications, 1973-1974 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Communications, 1973-1978 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Communications, 1974-1976 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Communications, 1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Communications, 1975-1978 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Communications, 1976 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Communications, 1979 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Communications, 1980 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Communications Conference, 1974 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Communications Network, 1971 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Community College, 1971-1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Community College, 1976 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Conferences, 1973-1977 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Conferences, 1974-1976 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Conferences, 1974-1978 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Conferences, 1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Conferences, 1977 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Conference Procedure, 1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Constitution, Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Contract Rider, 1972 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Coordinators, 1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Credit Hours, 1974 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - CUNY, 1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Delegate Lists, 1977-1981 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Democratic Platform, 1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Directories, 1974-1976 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Disabled Students, 1976 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Debts Due, 1980 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Dormitory Rent, Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Dormitories, 1980 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Election Law, 1976 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Entertainment, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Entertainment, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - EOP/AA, [1978]-1979 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - ERA, 1970-1973 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Faculty Tenure, 1974 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Federal Election, 1976 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Fees, 1976 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Fees, Fines and Deposits, 1972 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Financial Aid, 1973 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Financial Aid, 1974 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Financial Aid, 1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Financial Aid, 1978 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Financial Aid, Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Financial Statements, 1977 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Financial Statements, 1978 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Faculty Student Association, 1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Faculty Student Association, 1978 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Faculty Student Association, Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Foundation, 1973 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Foundation, Undated (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Glass, Ray, 1975 (Box 2 (6-Subject Files), Folder 58)